Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection 1890-1970 AD.MC.002
AbuDhabi
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971 (Box 1-7)
  - A young woman wearing a long skirt sitting on the grass in front of some foliage. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 22 April 1957; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Arabic Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gelibolu, Turkey; Individual Portraits; Parks; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two men on a prop boat named Sphinx. Studio background with trees and the moon. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Sedefgian Photographe, Place Ataba-el-Khadra, Cairo, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Boats; Cairo, Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A woman wearing a striped white dress and necklace holding onto a curtain. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio L. Missak, Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Fashion Accessories; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman wearing a long beaded necklace sitting on a bench with a bouquet in her hand. 13.4 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Egypt; Flowers; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Makeup; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman wearing a patterned chiffon dress with a pearl necklace sitting on a chair. Same table and background from ref187 and ref223. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Egypt; Fashion Accessories; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman wearing a satin dress and pearl necklace, sitting in a chair with a letter in her hands. Same table and backdrop from ref186 and ref223. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A man in a Bedouin costume with a sword, against a painted backdrop. Same studio backdrop as ref190. 13.5 x 8.4 cm, Circa 1922; Studio Vincent Photo Egyptienne, Rue Abdine No. 6, Caire (Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Costumes; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Swords & Knives; Traditional Dress
  - A man in traditional Upper Egyptian clothes with a young boy standing next to him. 14.0 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Boys; Egypt; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress; Turban
  - A young man with a mustache in a Bedouin costume, holding a a sword. Same studio backdrop as ref188. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 1922; Jacques, Vincent P.; Studio Photo Egyptienne, Egypt; Studio Vincent Photo Egyptienne, Rue Abdine No. 6, Caire (Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Arabic Writing; Costumes; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Swords & Knives; Traditional Dress
  - A woman wearing a beaded necklace, sitting on a bench with her feet on a cushion. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - A young woman wearing a heart-shaped necklace. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Cairo Studio (Egypt); Kofler, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Cairo, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman wearing a dark dress with circles, reclining on a chaise longue. 8.5 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Ramses, Cairo, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Cairo, Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman wearing a black dress sitting on a bench. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, 1908; Studio Isidore (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Arabic Writing; Clocks & Watches; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography; Women
  - A young boy standing in front of some potted plants and a watering can. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Boys; Children; Egypt; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants
  - Two women talking under a parasol on the beach.. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Beaches; Clocks & Watches; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Jewellery; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two young girls wearing light colored dresses. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, 1951; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools / Education
  - A woman in a dark dress holding a small white flower. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography; Women
  - A man in traditional Upper Egyptian clothing, leaning on a white ornate table. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Ramses, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress; Turban
  - A young girl in an Ottoman style dancing costume in a garden. 13.1 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Children; Costumes; Dancing; Egypt; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress
  - Two woman posing in an open-top car. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Cars; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A man sitting on chair with crossed legs, wearing a suit and bow tie. 13.3 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Bow Ties; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography; Suits
  - A couple holding hands, the woman wears a pearl necklace. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio Badr (Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Couples; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Women
  - A family group with three boys. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Boys; Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Women
  - An older female in a light colored dress sitting in a chair and leaning on a table. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography; Women
  - A young boy on a tricycle wearing a tarbouche. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Arabic Writing; Bicycles; Boys; Children; Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - A hand painted photo of a man in military uniform standing in front of a prop with a plant on it. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hand-colored Photographs / Hand-tinting; Individual Portraits; Men; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uniforms
  - Three women wearing dresses and headbands. 13.5 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Studio Aziz & Dores, Photographes, 3 Rue de L'Hopital Grec, Alexandrie (Alexandria, Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Alexandria, Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman wearing a dark colored head scarf, posing with three children in a garden. 14.1 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Boys; Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Head Covers; Maritime Outfits; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two women and two girls having a picnic on the beach. 14.1 x 9.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Beaches; Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Hats; Photographic Prints; Picnic; Women
  - A group of men posing next to and on a train. Photographer, I. Feldman Phot. Minia. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Feldman, I.; Photo Minia (Egypt); Studio Feldmann, Photo Minia (Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Ceremonies; Events / Occasions; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Minia, Egypt; Minya, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Train Station / Railway Station; Trains
  - A group of eight men in front of a painted backdrop. One man on the right wears a bow tie. 8.4 x 13.5 cm, 13 February 1924; Studio Bridge, 6 Bridge Road, Woolston (England) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Arabic Writing; Bow Ties; Egypt; England; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Handkerchief; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Southampton, England; Studio Photography; Suits
  - A man in military uniform with some medals, standing on a street with buildings in the background. 13.2 x 8.6 cm, 1 July 1945; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Arabic Writing; Buildings; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Medals; Men; Military / Soldiers; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Trees; Uniforms
  - A man wearing a suit with a bow tie and flower. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 1930; Studio Photo Venus, 3 Rue Emad-El-Dine, Ataba, Le Caire, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Ataba, Cairo; Bow Ties; Cairo, Egypt; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Handkerchief; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Signature; Studio Photography; Suits
  - A family group, a woman, young girl and two young boys wearing suits. 13.5 x 8.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Boys; Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Jewellery; Makeup; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography; Women
  - A man in military uniform standing in front of a painted backdrop. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Military / Soldiers; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Swords & Knives; Tiles; Uniforms
  - A man wearing a suit with a jacket over his shoulder standing on a street. 12.7 x 8.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Streets; Suits
  - Two girls with long hair, wearing white dresses. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography
  - Two boys on bicycles, posing in a garden. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Bicycles; Boys; Children; Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Photographic Prints
  - A young female, seated in a white dress with a bouquet in her hand. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Egypt; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman seated in a high backed chair wearing a dress with button detailing. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Cairo Studio (Egypt); Kofler, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - A young woman sitting on a table posing with a book, in a dark dress. same props and backdrop as ref186 and ref187. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Books; Clocks & Watches; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A family group, a young boy is standing on a bench next to his mother. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, 1923; Studio L. Missak, Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Boys; Cairo, Egypt; Family; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman with a hula hoop resting her feet on a cushion. 13.2 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Makeup; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Sports; Studio Photography; Toys; Women
  - Two men seated on an ornate bench and a woman standing in between them. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Signature; Studio Photography; Women
  - A young man in underwear, crossing his arms. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Arabic Writing; Boys; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Underwear
  - A family group, two younger women are wearing white dresses and have matching hairstyles 13.6 x 8.7 cm, 15 October 1928; Studio Photo Ramses, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Family Portraits; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Jewellery; Men; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography; Suits; Women
  - A girl resting on a chair, with a table and book behind her. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, 15 March 1930; Studio Photo Helios, Cairo, Egypt; Zoulis, C. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Books; Cairo, Egypt; French Writing; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Two young men walking with linked arms. 13.3 x 8.1 cm, 8 March 1940; Willy Kellermann, Photo Service, 38 Boul. Saad Zaghloul, Alexandria (Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Alexandria, Egypt; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Shops; Streets; Studio Photography; Suits; Walking
  - A family group, posing with two goats. 13.5 x 8.4 cm, 20 April 1930; Studio Fotografia F.S.M. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Animals; Buildings; Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Goats; Italian Writing; Italy; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A woman posing with an parasol on a beach. 14.1 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Beaches; Egypt; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Women
  - A man wearing a suit standing in front of a waterfall. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 18 July 1936; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Nature; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - A man wearing long robes sitting surrounded by four children. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Flowers; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress
  - A young man with a bow tie posing with a magazine. 13.5 x 8.2 cm, 19 December 1935; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Bow Ties; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Magazines; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Signature; Studio Photography
  - A bride and groom, the bride holds some flowers. 13.4 x 8.4 cm, 1922; Antoine, Albert (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Brides; Couples; Egypt; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Dresses; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils; Women
  - A Christian family group, a young girl is wearing a cross. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, 1923; London Studio, Cairo (Egypt); Studio London, Cairo, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Children; Coptic Cross; Family Portraits; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Studio Photography
  - Three males with tarbouches sitting on a large rock, 'Casino Corniche' is in the background. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, 1920; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Beaches; Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress
  - A woman with round glasses wearing a long patterned dress. 13.5 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio Nasib Habib, Faggala Street No. 78, Cairo, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Cairo, Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two girls wearing striped dresses and dark hair bows. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A woman lying down on the beach in front of huts. 8.7 x 11.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Beaches; Egypt; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Four males in suits and tarbouches posing against a painted backdrop. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 16 October 1920; Studio M. Khaled (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Signature; Studio Photography; Suits
  - A postcard of Place de la Concorde, Paris, France. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Arabic Writing; Buses; Carriages & Coaches; Cars; Eiffel Tower, Paris, France; Gelatin Silver Prints; Horses; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Place de la Concorde, Paris, France; Tram
  - An Egyptian man in front of the Eiffel Tower (duplicate). 14.0 x 9.0 cm and 13.0 x 9.0 cm, 11 November 1958; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Arabic Writing; Architecture; Coats; Eiffel Tower, Paris, France; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Paris, France; Photographic Prints
  - A family posing in Bedouin costumes. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated; E. Pappazoglou, Rue Bawaky 12 & Posta 15, Le Caire, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Cairo, Egypt; Children; Costumes; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress; Women
  - A family group of seven. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, 2 July 1934; Studio Photo London, M. Galoyan, Alexandria, Egypt (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Alexandria, Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Two men in three piece suits and ties. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
  - An Armenian family group with a small child sitting on a stool. Armenian text on reverse: From Mr. and Mrs. Asafian. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, April 1936; Photo - Studio Max, 53 Rue de Belleville, Paris, France (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Armenian Writing; Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Painted Backdrops; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A young woman holding a side table with a vase. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, 4 May 1927; Studio Photo Arax, 5 Haret Momtaz, Rue Mohamed Aly, Caire (Cairo, Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Cairo, Egypt; French Writing; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A boy in a sailor's outfit, leaning on a wicker chair. 13.9 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Boys; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Maritime Outfits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A woman in a décolleté dress and a matching veil. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 8 August 1956; Studio Akl, Aley (Lebanon) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Aley, Lebanon; Arabic Writing; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A belly dancer posing on stage. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Studio Isis (Egypt) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Belly Dancers; Dancing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Stage; Studio Photography; Women
  - A belly dancer posing in front of a curtain. 13.4 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Arabic Writing; Belly Dancers; Dancing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A family group, the man wears glasses and a suit. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Children; Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A portrait of Bebe Adham, a belly dancer posing. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Hussein Bekir, Egypt (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Arabic Writing; Belly Dancers; Dancing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A young man and two young boys wearing matching outfits. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Boys; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
  - A woman posing wearing a short jumpsuit. 8.7 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Studio Photo London, 13 Rue Emad El Dine, Cairo (Egypt) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Arabic Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Makeup; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Shoes; Studio Photography; Women
  - A family group of five, three adults and two children. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - An Armenian family, the young boy is in a nautical outfit. Armenian text on reverse: (signed) Hovakim 13.5 x 8.2 cm, 3 March 1935; Studio Photo Beyrouth (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Armenian Writing; Boys; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Maritime Outfits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - An older couple, female in a ruffled dress, seated on a bench. Sawides, Haiffa, Palestine. 13.3 x 8.4 cm, 25 October 1936; Studio C. Sawides Photo, Haifa, Palestine (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Couples; Gelatin Silver Prints; Haifa, Palestine; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Women
  - A young woman and a little girl pose cheek to cheek on a bench.13.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - An Armenian woman in a black dress. Armenian text on reverse: Nupar Terterian's mother. 13.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Armenian Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - An Armenian family. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, 18 November 1932; Studio C. Sawides Photo, Haifa, Palestine (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Armenian Writing; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Haifa, Palestine; Men; Painted Backdrops; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Two Armenian women wearing matching outfits. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Henri 11, Place de la Republique, Paris (France) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Armenian Writing; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Makeup; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Two females, one wearing round, dark rimmed glasses. Armenian writing on the reverse. (Rosa Alpasian and Araksya Asafian) (linked ref96). 8.5 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Eraskoff, V.; Studio Photo Russe, Egypt (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Armenian Writing; Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women